Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
Welcome to the cold, where the Wi-Fi's curse and the truth gets kidnapped
Gently then rehearsed, where the shadows talk back and the terror throw shade
And the guests on the panel look fresh from a side quest raid
We got chaos in the challenge, wisdom in the dark, a trope reward on the door
They still get in, but not far
If you're looking for a meaning, babe, you're right on track
Just don't ask Google, ask the voices whispering back
So loose in your halo
We're the only couple where the snacks are good
Welcome to where the wind gets holy nightly
Where the prophecy hits politely
And the jokes cut deep but lightly
Yeah this is the code of psyche
Where your shadow dances brightly
If you're lost don't worry highly
Likely that we planned it
Slightly
We're not a real couple
But like we're all so not not we got candles Lord and a membership spa
We got cosmic punch lines astrology T and the algorithm chained in the back making coffee your higher self
Please I'll get a sneak some sins the middle self. Oh, we just showed up for fun. None of us are whole
to the cold of psyche where the wild feels warm and inviting where the truth comes out
fighting biting but damn the lighting is exciting yeah this is the cold of psyche where the loss
feels strangely mighty come nightly where the shadows glow and the strange fits tightly
You got to clear your history and put an ad blocker on it's crazy.
Sorry.
They only have this clip on, on porno sites for some reason.
Oh my God.
Some lady came in ice because I guess I was backstage, but yeah,
I played the, I played the dolphin thing again.
Um, yeah, fortunately it was on a porno site.
And so then it makes this AI porn commercial came up where the woman was
very, I know exactly how those commercials pop up, buddy.
You got it.
That's okay, I mean handle that shit. You know what I mean, but jerk off to it. I mean, come on
I don't it's not that good
Okay, the dolphin made her shoot a load at SeaWorld. Oh
My that's not appropriate. She shot a load. No the dolphin made her shoot a load SeaWorld
Or but I think something came out of his blowhole, I'm not sure Jesus Christ
Anyway, Pornhub, Pornhub, it was, it's called,
this is a website called, it's called.
He just jumped up and came on demand.
Can call it luxury TV and it says AI porn is here
and it's fucking good.
And then there's one with like,
it looks like glue on our kids.
Or else he's like lactating like three diamonds.
And then the other lady, yeah, they didn't look real.
And then I see that, and I see that,
I see some big,
It would be a scary place
if men could ejaculate on demand.
Can you see me when I was when I was a teenager?
Can I just say that she belongs to the seas?
Yeah, she belongs to yeah, I think she I think she made a deal with Ursula there. I'm not sure
I don't know what just a no little mermaid shit going on. Yeah, that was that was little spermade little spermade
Hey, how'd your face brothers up peeking us behind that fucking creepy ass go?
Yeah, that's just Canada dry his regular face. Yeah, what do you think he's sexy? He's kind of he's kind of like a twink like you like
No, I think I like that skull a little bit more like you like oh you like a skull
You're like a necrophile you're like a dead body
pervert
i think that's beyond pervert i don't even know if that's perverted well in you know in india
they would do meditations on like a corpse of like somebody that died and then like
because there's like a lot of them laying around yeah they're also like one billion
word of the population they're also scumbags and you also smell
They're wonderful people. They're wonderful people.
Have you ever heard Indians sing Christmas songs?
That's like you saying, that's like me saying, hey, there's water hunger.
And you say, like, no, I eat. It's like, okay, the exception doesn't make the rule.
We're up to hunger. It's still a thing.
Well, only because it works on generalizations, brother.
Well, all they need to do is more cocaine and they'll eat less, right?
Okay, I don't think they have a but I think they have a problem with not I don't know you just confuse me
Oh, we have another guest our Indians that are our Indians that
Who's this? Oh
I saw I saw you over camera for a second Alex. That was pooper scooper. Wasn't it?
I
Know it know it in the ocean. I was gonna block you in the chat cuz a you said he reported you
Maritime world instead of cornhub they have prawn hub, right? I
Like yelling at people man. It's good. But you know what I like kicking people in the chat that are losers that attack like a yo
I like he's the one so he basically by him saying reported means when you got palm bombs he reported you whoever AO is
Lives to lead us there's nothing to report. It's like they can they can like say oh, there was something
But it's like the leaders. They don't really care. I mean you tap it in the million times
People always will try to do that like that's what they're trying to do. There's not a friendly person. Yeah, it's my phone. Yeah
Yep, there's a lot of people
I mean, I mean, Bita ended up striking me. I mean, it's like that's crazy. I mean, that's like
You're both shut the fuck off that fuck those can of dry
The fuck about you, I might do some more cooking. Can you do it naked and I can watch later? No. Yeah, can you do a naked?
a little apron
Can you pick up some bitches dream? It was a good one Canada dry can make me a little Canada wet. Oh
That's a that's name of his girlfriend. Don't say that Canada. What is his girlfriend's name? I thought I met her tonight
Oh, it's Canada dry and Canada wet. It's kind of cute, right?
You're still with that woman
Yeah
Canada's I called the Canada Club soggy
Because Ryan we're gonna do it naked. I'm not allowed to talk about beat us as well
You want them gone? You want them gone? Yes? Get rid of them out. I
Can actually I have the power to do that too, but you can do it. Just have fun
get him out of this. He always shows back up on Fred Allister 4, Fred Allister 5, Fred Allister 6,
then then now it's my name and there's my picture. Look how nice I look in that photo. I don't think
Syrax is making my picture. He makes me all bald and disgusting. Oh, I'm so mad about it. But oh,
did you see Syrax started a new YouTube channel and there's a little video he made or not he didn't
make it. It was actually his, his enemy made it, but
Um, it's a great animation. Let me see if I could just a couple minutes long.
CyRex got it. He started a new YouTube channel, but it got taken down within half an hour.
Um, so that's not very good. Um, what was it? Okay, so let me see. The worst person on the internet,
CyRex, um, yeah, he is pretty much...
One of the worst people I'm using this Marty's to troll him though. Okay. I have to look for the guys in there
Hold on. It's a Christopher Azazel is the guy that does the piss channel
Azazel is a nice angels name too. Okay, and it's Cyrax. Okay, so this is why why is sweepy harassing not a fallen angel though
Yes, he was a fallen angel, but he taught like astrology and stuff people pretty cool
Also the dude from x-band. He was the teleporter. He was red
Hey, so listen to this you fucking
Trolls I got a thousand dollars right here, bro
And I got a brand new motherfucking up Xbox series X. I will send all that shit to Cyrax
Thing I love I was saying that shit. I'm not no buddy troll. I'm not none of that shit. I swear to God
I was saying that shit. This ain't no, this ain't no bait.
Okay
Well, that's that's some cash demand. He's pretty terrible, but where's this like when he starts the channel?
It's cancer. I mean, there's like really strange stuff. Let me see
Bring Cobra's
Deep cuts on music Bismarie. Fuck. Yeah, Cobra's are sick
Or we can look it up here
We're the tunnel snakes and we rule follow up for yet
It's more on
Video
My girl said that I've been away for long and done.
Dime that my trolls are missing the fuck out of their boy.
Damn fucking bad.
Anyway, let's see. Channel name, done.
Don't let our work done.
Got my microphone ready, voice modulator ready,
hey what the fuck yeah my channel didn't even exist for more than a half hour
fuck you william glory dates if you think this is gonna stop me you better
i can't be stopped i'm a fucking god
I have the power, and I don't care no matter what this whole thing can do. Trust me, when I say this you can't tell me, why do you feel you have the right to call my name?
are a long time with your screaming oh that's gross Bob I didn't think I know
that besides if I don't confront my trolls dead my life will be at rest my
family will be at rest oh god damn it if they break our internet again you're
gonna have to get a job
I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit, I can't keep doing this shit
Rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
If so, what the fuck are you watching sir X is I wish I had three arms cuz I could get that shit three thumbs down. Oh
How about three fingers in my butt?
Hello anything is more productive
I'll be back shortly. You can ask him
Okay, you couldn't deal with that shit, but fuck with him
What what are you talking about tell me sir X?
It took him back to his childhood. It's fucked him up, man. You owe Alex
Have you seen like what sweepies does to me in her videos like, you know
I like beat it so mad because I made her look like an attractive geisha. Yeah, it was a geisha looks like
Buddy, you're talking to me about people. I can't stand the people who come in your chat and troll me and make videos and all that shit
I can't stand those fucking people. I don't know why you let them hang out in the chat
Let them I mean, it's like not like I can do very much. They have a thousand all
I don't even know who's who anymore it's just fucking block them all man. They're all fucks
Yeah, I'm about boo boo kitty who fuck that kid
It's like every first of all every
Picture big time investing that guy's a fucking
grease ball man that
Fucking he's he's my friend
I kind of think it's ghost salt accounts to be honest
Oh, here's my here's my channel. Okay. Oh, it says
Guys look what you did to me and beta says oh, it's just it's just teasing look at this look how offensive this is
Look my hair line. My hair is like that. It's beautiful like long
This is not me
I saw a clumsy bean gang, he was saying, hey, Samman has a nice ass.
I was up to the guy or I was in jail or something, I was, fuck Samman.
And I really like, I wish I had like control of J-Dog, like I could,
because if that'd be fun, like I could just like, go, I could just make him a sex slave and stuff.
I've always been like, bosom buddies, you know?
Okay, yeah, sure man.
And I pulled away
Do you know Sherman I'm done, but I was like sure man, Katie would say well
Oh, Alex
I was like, you know, we talked about it pulling to like, you know, cut down a little bit on the
oh my god i'm lucky i'm just on balls and stuff are you waiting for the man who comes here
no man i'm doing my dishes okay
well too one time i did shopolis like a huge thing of um pistachio like i could have gone for
like a little bag of pistachios but i went for like the five pound bag and this huge thing of pistachio
This is a few years ago, guys, I don't recommend doing that because if you're hungry, I walk
out of the store and the lady, I don't like to work there or something, but she started
screaming that I had a pistachio, so I started running on the street, a huge bag of pistachio
nuts from my pants.
Well, too.
One time...
Yeah, pistachio I'll play one more clip. This is the this is Canada dry explains the economy
Hey for $2 a day. I needed a bit of pride. Somebody came through for me and they're reading and everything
Hey psyche in Canada. You can't buy anything for five dollars. I said five
I didn't say anything about ten. Oh, you're gonna get a flex riled up
Alex, if he hears this right, he's going to be right up here.
He's lying to stir it up.
It's weird.
We're not as low.
Nope.
Fucking apple slices are $2.
For apple slices.
Alex, where are you, buddy?
Get out of here.
Oh, man, Alex.
Apple slices.
I'm going to kick you out of the show.
No, Samantha.
You can't buy anything from me.
That is content. That's amazing.
You kicked yourself out of the show, dude.
No, Samantha, you can't boom.
Oh my God. Alex, where are you at, bro?
I got kicked. What the fuck just happened?
Sorry. Oh, I don't know. I'm in my kitchen.
Yeah, you can't buy apples slices for, well, you know, McDonald's models thing for like,
you know, 99 cents. And so I don't know how expensive they are in Canada.
They're double everything is double in Canada. I remember I used to get a book and then it would say like USA like 495
They would say you can like 695 early. Oh my god
Stuff to live there. I was like everything's like $3 more
But then I found out it's kind of like just like they have a different currency a little bit, right? No things are more expensive
Yeah
sure
Surely are we have also thinking about all the all the all the pre-medical care you get all the you know alright
You don't know anything about our meta. Well, you know, kind of Canadian
Canada is actually fucking failing as a country
I've introverted blackface and I was you guys are literally getting taken over
You're gonna be fucking India pretty soon. Yes, a lot of us are leaving
Where are you gonna go? No, just like a lot of America
A lot of people are moving to northern areas that are less the things that are happening in the city
Yeah, so it's fucking country. Don't come over here. We don't want your asses
Okay
No
But yeah, I'm trying to be mean we don't want you point blank period bro, that's I'm not complaining
I didn't ask it to be like, okay
Okay, as long as you got that straight
I don't give a fuck, man.
What's wrong with you, Canada? Why are you so upset?
Yeah, are you gonna come over here and ask him for a silo?
Yeah, bro.
Hello. Thank you. Please come over here.
Can you sing O Canada? Is that the name of your root national anthem? O Canada?
O Canada.
Our home and native land, true patriot, in all our sons command, with glowing hearts we see the Lord strong.
And that shit sounds horrible
He plays a key, locks up, and we lock the door.
What the fuck was that?
Was that Hitler?
Yes.
I don't know, he's a good painter.
He's a good guy?
No, he's a bad guy.
He was a bad painter, but he was like...
He was just a very bad wizard.
He knew Germany first.
And he also, I mean...
He had some bad things, but...
He did what...
He trumped Germany.
He trumped Trump.
I mean, it's like, he's doing crazier things than Trump is doing.
But, you know what?
We don't have to live under him.
Right?
Well, I'm not yeah, I'm just making French toast buddy
Aren't you making a Canadian creator aren't you Canadian?
makes French Canadian toast on French toast
Little some maple syrup. No syrup. It'll make me
Hot honey on everything kind of is like I think I'm like slightly allergic to it, but oh my gosh
Yep
Yeah, honey, there's bees in the
Fuck you up
Killer bees in the Amazon and they go in what they're gonna be honey. Okay. Yeah, there's a plant
It's called more dressed because they're after rhododendron. Oh my god, the rhododendrons that wrote it from the marriage of immortal. Oh
Okay, well, they go and they get all the rhododendron sap and it's hallucinogenic
And so when people ingest their honey, it's like doing drugs
Is that what happens to you I wonder if it's the same thing if an animal would ingest it
I bet it would be well, you know, you can lick it you can lick a toad and get high
So why not you can also die from it too because it's toxic, but that's what all good drugs are like slightly
That mad honey, bro
I seem like the
Documentary where they like fucking they climb up those mountains on like like yeah, man
They're getting stung and they don't give a fuck basic candy bodies and in a honey like they'd have the person
A lot of those people don't even get stung though
It's weird isn't it isn't that kind of weird how they don't get stung like beekeepers
They can go in there without a suit on and not get stung like how the fuck does that work?
I don't care how calm you're walking
Probably because the bees recognize them. Oh fuck. Here comes the first thing. Maybe. I think some of those guys also get tolerant to stings
It's like they've been stung hundreds of times over 30 years. Oh no, especially with a hornet a hornet bees bad enough pain tolerance, bro
You know, it's worse. Some people have higher pain tolerance
And they say, you know, if you get stung and you're like, I only like go like this and you french down you get stung more
I guess, you know
Yeah, but how about a wasp don't you get stung don't you get stung don't flinch just fucking take it I guess
What?
But they walk like there's nothing going on with them
Mod Jamie's a beekeeper, you know
And she's a beekeeper
Cheers
I'm
Yeah
What panel did Alex join
I'm not fucker went somewhere interesting
What's interesting
Who psyche you're Alex Alex. Hi, buddy went somewhere. Fuck you're tripping me out, buddy
You hear that French toast trying on the pan there I did hear that
It's kind of nice, there it goes.
Cookin' with Canada's dry
You can try
Come on by
It's a world of culinary imagination
Bring your knives
But not your wives
We don't want them in our beauty kitchen
Our super efficient kitchen
We are cooks
You are clowns
Sing it, buddy, sing it.
This panel, there's a lot of air in here.
What's going on, guys?
Thank you.
Oh, gosh.
I don't know why he's playing like white people music.
Like, I want him to be listening to like a Mexican person.
And he's like, and one more time.
I think he's listening to like emo stuff.
That's kind of weird, isn't it?
Yeah, I bet he likes Marilyn Manson more than he likes, you know
Who's that guy South Park five or whatever? Marilyn Manson's good. Yeah. Yes. Well, I'd like
Have you like this stuff lately? I assume it's kind of okay, but um, you're right. I prefer early man
Yeah, I mean, I've been in several Marilyn Manson concerts, too. Really? Yeah
It was Hull and Marilyn Manson, but Hull quit the show after the show I was at, and then
Manson came on after Hull and broke his rib within five minutes and quit the tour.
Or he, like, you know, the show was over.
And I was on ecstasy.
I was like 17 or 16 years old, and all of a sudden, relations came up and everyone's
like all normal.
And I was like, oh, fuck, because I was just, like, turning to a role.
Hey, what's up?
That's crazy, man, that you saw Hull and Marilyn Manson.
Yeah, it was pretty cool.
I've seen Hull a few times.
I've seen Manson a few times.
Really?
Did you like Hull, or were they just opening for people?
I was more there to see Hull than to see Marilyn Manson,
but I did turn into a person for that one.
But um yeah because I just like I mean by that time I think like I would there's just a few like
bands like there was like you know the beautiful people and like sweet dreams and then it's like
why specifically were you in the hole like what was it about hole that you like
Because Courtney and Love, I just thought she was like,
first of all, there's not that many,
like, I think really, really wonderful,
like female rockers, you know?
And I really liked her voice.
I liked her, the baby doll style.
And then I was like, also, I was like a Nirvana fan,
kinda like, but I was around like 12 or 13
when he unalived himself, right?
So I was like,
You know interesting so you grew up and then you're like now I can go see his his ex like yeah
But what he loved but she's also I remember I liked her album a lot her first one like well
And actually I even like her album like she has a more punk album called pretty on the inside
It's before I lived through this or whatever and it's like really good. So yeah sounds a lot like a female nirvana
Yeah, well, she like he wrote a lot of her music. That's the thing
It's like and she there's actually even a clip of the song called live through this or he's like on the song
And she actually cut out of the song and he's it's on it's on her album
It's a whole album to live through this actually he probably made the reference track or something
Yeah, I think that he was just a very talented guitarist musician in general. She was like she has this talent
I mean she burned out. Do you think she killed him or no?
Yeah, I think she tried. Well, she I think she tried to hire this guy
I know that she tried to hire this guy named El Duce
Yeah, he's weird like 50 grand. I think she offered him and he like he died right after he like said that and it's but it's like if you
The conspiracy angle of it like it's like how he would have been like so
The the man of heroin in the system was like you couldn't nobody even if you were like a
Really a lot right you wouldn't just casually do that
You're just like hold up a gun and like do that, you know, you'd be like just nodding out instead
It's like very hard to like, you know pick up a I don't know. There's just weird stuff about it. I don't know
and then she also said like Courtney loved like there's also a suicide note or you know and it's
like in two different hand writings and one of the hand writings I think it's her pre-obvious it's
her and then it's like also it worded in a way where it's and then it's written in oh say I love
my daughter blah blah and then Courtney Love also said that he he was he nodded out dropped uh Francis
and that's why he was like so guilty or something like that because he dropped well you're right that
Yeah, because there's also in two different hand-routings. It really was yeah. Yeah, and why did she have the suicide now?
Wouldn't that be like in the police's possession? Like how'd she get that suicide? I mean it's like just right. Yeah, I don't know
This is a bit of weird stuff, right because they said they checked everywhere and didn't find one
And then she found it under the pillow and the cops were like, um, we looked there
But it's like was something like that or am I wrong and also she was in rehab
And he was mostly in rehab at the time too
But then he like escaped rehab or he like left rehab or you to check himself out
And so I don't so I think she has an alibi because she was in rehab, right?
And she had the kid take it because there's this one that someone named Francis Farmer or who is this person home?
There's somebody named
No, no Lee Lynn Hershberger
Lynn Hershberger did it like a GQ article on Courtney Love that goes really harsh and she said like that because I guess she did an interview
With Courtney Love and then Courtney Love was on drugs and stuff like that and then Lynn Hershberger
Reported that she was on all these drugs, but unfortunately she was like, you know
single mom at the time and so she had the or not a single mom with her, you know
But she had the kid the kid taken away for a while. Yeah, Francis being of course he's a kid
She looks just like him of course. I mean Casey no one doubts that it's his daughter
Sometimes I wonder what Billy Corden's opinion of everything is because he he was so close to it and then he dated her. Yeah
He said he stayed in his opinion too like he said he I mean he he wrote her songs too for the album after look through this
Like she always he thought that she was like in like did sick. Oh, no, he really killed himself like what do you?
I think that it's like if you're in this, I mean, Billy Corgan is a little bit of like
an occultist and probably like a little bit like a conspiracy theorist.
I think, I think maybe he would think that's kind of like cool or I don't, I don't, I don't
know.
I see it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I get you.
Yeah.
It's interesting because when he was on Howard Stern, he talked about a female that was in
his life that supposedly shifted in front of him, like shapeshift or something.
I actually think people are shape-shifting, like, to put, like, um...
Tell me your shape-shifting experience.
Well, that was, like, the lady I dated, and it's, like,
when the shape-shifting was, like, during, during, like, a sexual kind of experience,
and I wasn't expecting it to happen, and especially, like, how it happened.
It's, like, if I learn later, verified, like, that it was, like, something unusual,
because I wasn't that really in the, I was not into Hinduism at the time, but she's, like,
It is like an Indian goddess and then it's like I found out all the stuff about Tantra and stuff about how well not to interrupt you
But I've heard a lot about this thing like during sex a clock in their face will contort and shit like this
And it's been like reported a lot
Yeah
like the energy changing and stuff and the mixture of the energy and it's like and it just is like it's some kind of
Magical experience, you know, we've all had this kind of magical experience
But it was like really like she was like an ad at it because it's like she was able to generate herself
And I don't know if it was like she believed it so much that I saw it or it's like I it was really really strange
But I mean she was because she was like a couple hundred pounds
Before and it's like and then she like yeah, and I'll be throwing colors and shake and stuff
I mean, I've been a few women with shaky eyes. That's kind of trippy thing and
Yeah, like I'm sure at least the Jordana too is that people call her reptilian and shapeshifter and stuff
I mean, I and even I
Mean, I think all of us have some kind of ability to
change or look a lot different especially women women are really good at
putting on disguises and stuff like that sometimes because it's like they just
change their hair and they're a different person you know but men can
as popular for them to look so different but hey you know how old Johnny Depp
Robin Williams and they're not Robin Williams Johnny Depp Tom Cruise and who
else Keanu Reeves are they're all in their 60s now and that's pretty crazy
But at least I know she's just she's a reptilian shaped where she embraces it and hey
If you're watching there's someone you told me a story about someone because you were talking about India and that like
Hindu and all that stuff as someone went to see some sort of like
And I'm gonna quote this wrong because I just kind of faintly remember to see some kind of guru
Fucking healer high level fucking seer type dude in India and the person
When they were having their session they were meditating put in there
No, he became her mother. Oh my god
And gave her information that only her mother like yeah
Like literally her mother came and gave her something she needed to hear and this she she told this story like this man
Completely changed into my mom
and I'm not, but he was able to meditate me
or do something that it was,
I'm trying to think where I'm going to go.
I mean, I think it's,
what you're saying is not unusual to me
because if you study like, you know,
Like like I'm Kaula, which is like kind of like the dark like the darker kind of taunt row at elder
They actually have an India. They have this thing called
Like, you know, we're Shiva, you know, Shiva's like a beautiful. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, like Kali
Kali and Shiva rubber means a dead body, right?
I'm sure and so and also you can see like Shiva is like laying down the color blue like a dead box
like I mean, he's like portrayed as a dead body sometimes because he's like the
material and then she's like the energy or like the Shakti which is like this is like the
great energy that is like you know responsible for people reproducing and
like a lot of like a lot of crazy things like it's a there's Krishna Vishnu yeah I mean there's
like a there's a couple the couple trinities because it's like if you read about the Tantra it will say
it was like before any other god like when you're like that's like little kids like learn all
that's like the elephant one okay right but it's like there's a saying in India it's like a it's
like a uh my hammock goes shiva shakta yukto yali bhavati shakta prabhavitum
It means Shiva is Kali and Kali is Shiva, like one cannot do anything without the other
pretty much, and without one, neither is dead, and they're movable.
And then together, they create this dynamic force.
And also that they are...
Like they're the real couple having sex everyone else is kind of just like little reflections having sex based on their other on this like
Cosmic on a huge like if you I don't know just I think about things it goes into science and things like that
It goes I mean it's like there is
Their systems are so beautiful and like there's so much the oldest religion right and do well. Yeah, I mean yeah, I mean I would say
You know, they're like I would say they're there's a lot of tribalism that's old and I would say even like, you know
Early Judaism is was it Hebrew? I say they even before the Hebrews like the Phoenicians
Which are like, you know, people like they're the people that were like the merchants that developed the language
So they could be merchants and things like that, right? But also
Christianity grew out of Judaism and then Muslim or an air and Arabic grew out of
Christianity and so they all have the same
forefather, which is Abraham, you know, father Abraham. And so they're all Abrahamic. Abraham
means brother. So it's basically like the whole family, the religious supposed to be kind of a
family. There's also like, I've studied Buddhism, like Tibetan Buddhism, and they basically had
somebody from Afghanistan named Padmasambhava came over and he taught to like Buddhism to the whole
kind of
people and everything and like he subdued all these demons and there's just this beautiful magical
story the art is incredible like the there's um but it's like very similar to like some stories
about Jesus you see these universal stories everywhere like right yeah so they were passed
around I don't know just by the sea people or what but the Phoenicians that there's a very
important person or people to study that they are the discoverers of the purple the color purple
because they could find these snails and get the,
they were so excited.
Really?
They were the first people to use the color purple.
And they made it, they made these like,
they would sell the clothes to royalty,
but only purple, the royalty were the purple, you know?
Interesting.
Yeah.
Uh, and that is true. I mean, and, uh, well that's an interesting thing I never thought
of that back in the day when colors and dyes were harder to, uh, obtain that certain colors
would have been more expensive based on what they were used to make. I never really thought
about that.
It's so interesting, right? Like red would have been super easy to make.
Like a lot of colors were poisonous. Like the good, like they could get a beautiful blue
Painters would get sick and die early probably because they were drinking some of poison ink and the they're just like red M&M's
They had red M&M's in the 70s that had a cost cancer the red the red number two
And so they didn't have red animals M&M's for like a year
Gotta think that like back in the day like you know like we're talking
So this is a very early times times of spice trading basically
but like the color red would have been much easier to come by than let's blue or
Yeah, it's really interesting. Yeah, I mean, what how do you get you mean?
these colors from flowers and from like
stones right and they used to make ink out of
All kinds of things, you know, oh my gosh different colored dirt. Yeah, and um, I even like the earliest
Form of writing wasn't even with ink though. It was just into clay called Cunea even bugs, bro
They used to crush up different bug shells, right, right?
I mean you were saying snail for purple like they they use
Sea snails or sea snails. We had to be like at like dive they had to dive for them and stuff like that because
And so like it's uh, it they don't use lacquer very much anymore. They used to use it a lot on
Well, it's just like yeah, you can get something called castor and from beavers and anal glands and they make yes
That's in everything bro. That's shit in everything perfume
Something something indian came on it. This looks interesting though, which is funny right because there's so like people don't realize
how
The livestock and like that, you know that the agriculture
Isn't just for human consumption like like you said like
There's there's things that are used in everyday products that come from animals. For example, like the fat is in is in crayons, right?
Like well like I said like even like a species involvement is it like it like
Comes out and it like just like rocks on the top on the right ocean for like 500 years
And then it comes to the shore and it's like called amber grease and it's and it's like it smells delicious
And they put it in perfume and stuff, but it smells like like you know whale shit for the first like a hundred years or something
Right, so it's pretty crazy. Yeah
Amber I wonder how people discover this weird shit. They're like, huh?
But washes up on the on the no just all different things that are like, oh, yeah
From the fucking beaver ass and we're gonna put it in everything like it was the first person
Who was the first person to do that in the side? Oh, yeah, we maybe we should just try this
Let's just try guys. I know I think outside of the box, but
I don't think it
Oh, no
You what do you drop
My ball. Oh, no, is it broken?
No good
No
Thank you. Awesome. Okay, so what was I gonna show you though? Let me see. I think have you heard of um, let me see
Oh, yeah, Mojini
There's like this really cool
Avatar Vishnu and Mohini, but I like it when she's like in the I like the really crazy like real Indian videos
Like the when I was first getting into graphic design
I loved those images and I used to be a shnew a lot for some just different like
poster ideas because yeah, it's really cool
Ooh, actually, oh my, so yeah, well, yeah, so it looks like this is like, oh my gosh
She's really interesting. It's really interesting how everything
Like oh here this well, I mean, this is 30 minutes. I can't show I can only show like a one-minute thing
Let's see. Well, he needs to check the six million five million where God tricks. Hold on
I'll find something just very short, but anyway, so she but actually she had to come down like they're like trying to like
You know get the milk out of the ocean or something like that. Oh, it's a horror movie
Okay, a horror movie. Yeah
Well, that's what that one with horse that one. I just saw is there's one that's really good where she like she like
He's dancing and like she has she she just be she just keeps distracting like the male gods
You know for attention and stuff and then they
Pretty cool.
Well, her name means, like, a lesion.
Like, Maya is kind of, like, a similar name from it.
But it's, like, it's not a bad thing.
Like, Maya is very powerful.
Like, this illusion, and we are so sure we're
our ego and everything.
It's very, but it's, like, also, if we're come in a certain way,
it's very hard.
It's very, very difficult.
But it's, like, also.
It's like it's like also like fun and like it's like a good thing too. It's like a big game to her. So, okay
I should just I actually I mean like a little video about it. I'll show my video so I don't give I'm just I'm just cleaning up
This shit right now, but I'll check it out. Okay. Well, I'll put it on for everybody
It's only five minutes long. I think you see
Yeah, I got it. She's a Hindu goddess. I'm enchant. I hear you too
Here you go, some people have said I'm a Hindu goddess
Well, you you might be you know, there's more Hindu gods than there are like even like
People on earth. Are you serious? Yeah, there's like billions of them. I swear. Yeah, how
And they're all named or it's just like assumed that they exist.
I think that as plentiful as sands on the beach, just like, huh.
Welcome back to the cult of psyche wear with steady gods, glamours,
and the kind of cosmic finesse that makes your ex look like an amateur.
Tonight, Mohini. Not just a pretty face, not just a story.
Mohini is a spiritual technology, a living lesson and illusion, discernment,
and the way desire can hijack your entire operating system.
And yes, Mohini is funny.
because the universe has a sense of humor and it shows up wearing jewelry.
Quick disclaimer, this is reverent. We're not turning a sacred figure into a meme.
We're learning. We're looking at symbolism. We're extracting the medicine.
Jat-type Mohini if you're here for the nectar. Mohini is a form of Vishnu and Avatar.
A manifestation appearing as a mesmerizing woman whose presence bends attention like gravity.
Here's what's important. Mohini is not Vishnu pretending.
Mohini is Vishnu expressing a force. A force that says, if you can't control your desire,
your desire will control you. Mohini is the divine mirror that shows you what you've really driven
before and what's over me after the questionable decision. Mohini is like, I do.
Also, Mohini would absolutely dominate social media.
The algorithm would be in love.
The comments would be a war zone, and she'd still be unbothered.
Let's talk about the famous moment, the nectar of immortality.
Can you mute my mic?
Yeah.
Making a smoothie out of destiny.
Everyone else working together to bring out treasures, medicines, and the nectar.
And the moment that nectar appears, the vibe immediately changes because cooperation
But the second the prize arrives, everybody discovers their true self.
So the ones who wanted the nectar for themselves start posturing.
Grabbing, scheming, it's giving.
We were friends until the money showed up.
And this is where Mohini appears.
Not with a weapon, not with an argument, not with a lecture, with presence.
Mohini steps in and says, basically, relax, I'll distribute it fairly.
And everyone agrees, because they're enchanted.
Now here's the lesson, Mohini doesn't force anyone.
Mohini reveals them, if your will is weak, you will volunteer your freedom, you will
hand over your discernment and call it love, fate, or just one more time.
So, Mohini begins distributing the nectar strategically so balance is restored,
and the cosmic order doesn't get flipped by raw greed, and the story teaches this wild truth.
Sometimes the universe fixes chaos through elegance, not conflict.
Chat this is important, if you only respect power when it's loud, you're gonna miss
half of reality.
In some tellings, there's a character who tries to sneak into the right side of the
line and take what isn't meant for them.
Result becomes part of the Sky story and ongoing reminder that shortcuts don't disappear.
They transform into patterns.
That's what an eclipse is in this symbolic language.
A reminder that hunger without wisdom creates shadow.
So Mohini isn't just distributing nectar, she's distributing consequences.
Not everyone gets the same thing at the same time.
Fair isn't equal.
Fair is aligned.
Now let's hit one of the funniest stories attached to Mohini.
There's a figure who receives a blessing, a power that activates through touch.
And instead of using that power wisely, the ego immediately goes, I should be unstoppable
now.
Which is basically every dude who gets a little attention and starts acting like a pharaoh.
So Mohini appears not to punish but to demonstrate the shape of the trap.
Mohini begins to dance, a graceful hypnotic sequence, and the power-ungry figure mirrors
Mohini raises a hand so do they. Mohini turns so do they. Mohini touches so do they.
And the power they want it to use outward, turns inward. Lesson, if you can be manipulated by
flattery, you are not free. You are not sovereign. Mohini doesn't defeat them by force. Mohini lets
their own weakness complete the spell. That's why this story is hilarious and terrifying.
It's the universe saying, your biggest enemy is your unmanaged appetite. Chat type discernment
Let's go deeper. Mohini is often connected with the concept of male illusion, appearance.
The shimmering veil of reality.
But Maya isn't fake, it's the interface, it's how the infinite becomes visible,
it's how the formless communicates in form. Mohini is a reminder that beauty is power,
but it's neutral power, beauty can heal, beauty can guide, beauty can also hijack,
so the question isn't is, beauty dangerous? The real question is, are you conscious because
if you're not conscious, you'll treat your cravings like commandments. Also,
This is sacred shapeshifting. The divine is not boxed in.
Mohini says, your categories are smaller than reality. And that's not an argument.
That's a cosmic flex.
Ohini.
Here are the cults of psyche takeaways.
Dante negotiate with desire while you're under the spell.
If you're triggered, lonely, hungry, tired pause, breathe, drink water, sleep, then decide.
Watch who you become a round nectar.
Your nectar might be attention, money, status, romance, revenge, being right, whatever makes
you forget your values that's your test.
Mohini teaches strategy without brutality. You don't always need a battle. Sometimes you need a
boundary and a calm voice. Respect the tradition. Mohini isn't just a seduction story. It's theology,
symbolism, devotion, and cultural living reality for many people. If we're going to
borrow the wisdom, we borrow it with clean hands. So who is Mohini? Mohini is the spell that exposes
the spell. The beauty that reveals your hunger. The divine reminder that if you don't hold your
someone or something will hold it for you. And in cults of psyche terms, Mojini is the glamour
with a lesson stitched inside the hem. If you want, and Shiva, in the respectful versions,
and how that story becomes a teaching about paradox, devotion, and divine polarity, chat type
nectar if you want part to, stay sharp, stay sovereign, and don't hand your crown to a craving.
Here we go.
Interesting, I mean I like to I like to
So much being content and vision either the thought well
Do you know how much on one day on YouTube is enough?
Content is put on YouTube for one man to watch every day the rest of his life just 25 hours a day
Just one day. So think about how much
It's quite unusual hours and it's like there's just so much people that even gets on the algorithm or anything
and some people so many people just use it for different reasons, but
It's very crazy. And so yeah, we can have discernment about what we eat
It's gonna sound a moral commandment, but it's discipline if you don't
Right, I guess but you're you'll learn people learn one way or the other, right? It's like the universe kind of like does it dance with
people with this so
the thought of what it is
What brought it on the thought of that is what brought it on but you just oh, hon
Very good. Okay. You're chilling. Yeah, I
Also, yeah, I mean I've been enjoying like, you know Christine was talking about oh, he thinks life is a fairy tale
Well, first of all just because I I said I was raised on fairy tales doesn't mean I don't think life is a fairy tale
not that I don't because
Fairy tales aren't always just happy. I mean like they're very tragic and dramatic and a lot of
Things happen, you know that are like, you know these plot lines, but they the same things happen as people too
And it's like there are things we can relate to and it's also like a
We have like nostalgia too of like, you know, I think that the these ideas can live through stories
Like and that's why we should continue telling them and you know
I need an adult that can't enjoy a good story. Well, I don't know it's like
you know
There's a lot of story
Want to hear a story? I have a
It's reading rainbow
Anywhere I can't do anything open
Reading rainbow
Okay
Okay, I have, yeah, I have this Rumpelstiltskin.
I did a version of that.
Did you like that story?
If this is turning into story time,
then I'm Rumpelstiltskin.
Why Rumpelstiltskin?
Yeah, well, I go into it like I go into it. It's because you know
Everyone says he's like this evil character because oh he wants to make a deal with her or whatever
Can you do me a different look at the story of rumple force again? No, that was that's one of his cousins
I don't like that person very much or that
Hold on a second. Yeah, actually rumple still skin does mean balsak
I mean, I think that's what it is a nickname for but I don't think that's he
I don't know necessarily his choice for a name, but this is rumple for skins another guy
What really happened? Okay, and it's just it's just a short few minutes here. Let's let's enjoy some story time guys
Here we go. We'll still skin here we go
Hey, welcome back tonight. We're doing something a little different no guests no chat games
Just me this chair and a story a scary one. You know how fairy taleys work, right?
Girl in trouble monster in the dark heroes go to sleep children the world makes sense
except it doesn't
And the original versions of these stories before the
That's Alex in the woods, find in a bit.
Before the publishing houses decided children needed protecting from reality, they knew that.
The brothers Grimm weren't writing bedtime stories.
They were writing field reports, observations from the edge of something true.
Tonight's story is Rumpelstiltskin.
That's me and Psyche like holy fuck, Alex is out there fucking bitches.
Get inside.
Tells the king that his daughter can spin straw into gold. That's the coke dealer lies
The lies because he wants to seem important in front of power
And he uses his daughter's existence as the currency of that lie without asking her
Without warning her and here's where it gets interesting. No one saves her not her father
Not a guard who feels sorry for her not the king who put her there
A door opens in the dark and something small an ancient walks in and says I can help you
Next night same room bigger pile same threat same door same question. She gives him her ring
Third night and this is where the king decides he wants to marry her which is its own horror
We'll get to she has nothing left to give and the creature says promise me your first-born child and she does
Oh my god, the story wants you to feel a particular thing here
It wants you to feel dread it wants you to feel like she made a terrible mistake like she sold something sacred to a monster
But let's say she's going child king with a lie
The king imprisoned her under threat of death. Three times. Every man with power in this story
used her as a resource. And then in the dark something showed up and said I'll help you.
Here's my price. Do you agree? She agreed freely, three times, with full knowledge of the terms.
so she's a whore
not because she's one
she took the money
touch, touch
the baby came
She begs she weeps is born. She offers him wealth instead. Yeah, I know here. This is the part one find a very strange
He softens he gives her three days. He says if you can guess my name you keep the child
Why why does he do that? The story never explains it the grim version just presents it as a plot mechanism
He doesn't need her suffering
He made an agreement and the agreement is valid and he could simply take what he's owed, but he gives her a chance
Maybe, and this is the reading I keep coming back to, maybe the name was always the point.
Not the child.
The name.
Names are the oldest magic.
Every tradition that works with power knows this.
You name something, you have a relationship with it, you know its name, you have leverage
over it.
Rumpelstiltskin has been walking around nameless, or as good as nameless, for longer than kingdoms
have existed.
and here is a woman a woman who has survived three death threats a force to
everyone knows dates three and he gives her three days to name him she says
you're very mature 20-hours for 10 years I'm starting to fucking hate this story
but her own name was over her father's worthless word and on the third day her
messenger returns with a story deep in the forest a small creature dancing
around the fire singing a song with a name in it his name she says it he
or in some versions he tears himself in two, which is a specific kind of ending, not defeat,
not death, division, as if able to exist in the dark and the unnamed. Here's what I think the story
is actually about. It's about what happens when every person with power in your life treats you
as a means to their end. Your father, your original protector, trades you for status.
The castle, the gold, the crown, none of it is yours.
You are the mechanism by which other people get what they want.
And then something from outside that system appears and makes you a deal acknowledges your agency,
waits for your consent.
But the real horror, the horror the original tellers knew and the sanitized versions buried, is the castle.
The lie that fatherhood is protection when it's performance?
the horror that power calls itself love when it means ownership. Rumpelstiltskin wanted a name,
he wanted to be known. Maybe what he was collecting in all those deals across all those centuries
was proof that he existed, that something in the world would hold the shape of him long enough
to say it back. She guessed it, she said it, he shattered. And she was finally, for the first
That's the scary tale not the creature in the dark the men in the light who never asked her name at all
Good night cults. Stay strange. Oh
Shit deep as fuck
That's insane
That means basically she wasn't free till her parents died then she was free because they kept the caged in the whole life
And uh, is he sold her into did the key was like, you know for he wanted something. Yeah, her own family
He was there till whatever she was there in fairy tales
It's like if you look at Disney movies, there's something always fucked up with the natural mother, right?
She always is either dead or like there's always a stepmother or something like that
There's like very rare a great that's why everyone's fucked and unlike drugs and like psychiatry because all the parents are fucked
Well, you know these little kids grew up in these fucking homes with these crazy people
No, you know love but like fake love and it's just like we're going to some weird
Unlock me and your parents and your parents on us
They give it to you in a weird way and that hurts even more
When you know your parents love you to death and they'll do anything
But they're retarded and don't know how to like really be parents
That's fucked up
Take more than just toys and like money and toys and here then
And then hogs and hogs and kisses
The famous study that's like I think he's like I think I was like Pavlov or something
But or something but they can't give this son like a little like a fish tank or something
It's first three years of life and never like hugged him or anything and it's just like
That's insane
That's what I'm saying. I know people that don't kiss or like hug their parents. I'm like, what are you crazy like that?
My parents like that's a grew up in a family that that's it when you see your family members
You're like, yeah, I'm like, I don't get that. Some people don't do that. And that's the devil
Well, it's sad because I'm not like the father doesn't have to be there, right?
And so it's like so some people will have this like father that's very excited to be a father and some
Some father was just kind of like, you know, there would be a sperm donator for some people, you know
And it's like in the sand night organ donor
Well, no, not organ donor. You know, you're talking about like an organ
sperm donor sperm donor
The cognate has a lie. He's not a father. He's just a sperm donor. He's just king in the puzzle. It's okay. Yeah, it's fine
It's not like it's not like somebody that's gonna take somebody's like, you know
Kidney in the middle of the night. No
Those things happen, but I mean, I don't know how much now, but what is wrong with Trump?
Is this look at Trump's face right here, but he's with Elon Musk. Why do they look like
Shape chips just won. They look like something home. That was a weird picture. Oh my gosh, Bailey's man, all of them
There's a picture of him motherfuckers. Look at that. Oh here it is. Look look at this
Look at that tan
What's from what's going on there? He's like he's he's like
One is what is milk the other one's fucking has a spray. I find that funny. That's a that's a soft pork episode right there
Yeah, it's like shit sandwich and
Is that the and the
I forgot what the other one was what what guys will win how bro with these people at the helm
We get the most retarded humans at the helm right now. Well, because it's like they're all
compromised and so that they're I rather have psyche in the white house
Then what we have in there right now like we are fuck
You're not making any sense case. You're just bothering people when you say these jokes like you're being really deep
But then they don't make the link. Take the link KZ. Don't sit there
It's like
Just say something don't do shit. Yeah, just don't be a pussy. Yeah
Exactly I'm pussy pussy hit the link
Oh, thank you. Don't be afraid black or G's gonna come over and make fun of you with no teeth or some shit
Tats
Okay, suck a tad remember that but like when you when he made J. C. Stay suckering suck it that's
My pictures, this is just AI in the background
There's more ai in that one picture than in like all my songs put together
I mean it's like you look like that guy from like the impractical jokers guys. Why are we laughing though?
We should be like on our knees thanking god
People are getting bombed right now
We're lucky to be alive and we're at war and we're here like lol kz come on
Well, we're school of fucks
Well, that's good because you know, we'll see how lucky we are. Yeah, we are being bombed or whatever, but exactly
You should take a moment of silence for the for the war we don't have to endure
You know like at a baseball game. We take a moment of silence for the following
Thank you God for
Keeping us nice and safe here in the United States where we can order anything at the drop of an and I'm worried about missiles
Well, the whole plan is getting bumped into hell.
It's open and it says, it says, it's the first night.
And it says, I remember the day that war became real for me.
Not through a television screen or breaking news headline,
but at a bus station at Budapest under gray skies
and a cold wind.
I volunteered on instinct more than plan
to help the Ukrainian refugees pouring into Romania.
I owned a hotel and a few houses on the outskirts
of the city.
I decided I'd offer shelter.
What I was getting into, I just knew I had space and they had nowhere to go.
That day I drove to the bus terminal for the first time, a little nervous, a little unsure.
Children climbed out of the buses carrying bags and blankets in silence.
They looked like people walking out of a fire. Among them one woman stood out.
She was alone with her three daughters at her side, close in age, maybe between five and 12.
The kids clung to her coat like anchors. She noticed me as if sensing something safe
Yeah, and it says she had no fear just exhaustion in her eyes
He didn't speak the same language, but some things don't need words
And so I'll just skip ahead a little bit. That's crazy at a point fear here. Like I'm so tired
The fear goes out the window like fuck this shit. You still getting pissed last paragraph is she said she said
I smiled not because of what I saw but because of what it meant. I guess you saw like a warm room and
Lady was happy. She said this moment was the beginning the first refugee the first story
The first reminder that helping people wasn't going to be a clean straightforward thing
It would be very messy unexpected and human something in that night whispered to me not in words
But in a feeling this is only the beginning you have no idea what's coming and it was right. I don't know what I would
Go on to help hundreds nearly a thousand by the end. I would cry shout question everything laugh
I would eat kids who wouldn't speak old women who still believed in God. I would be used love old women
You still believed in God
I would give too much never regret it the first night stays with me because it wasn't just a funny unexpected moment
It was a reminder that every active humanitarian work
No matter how noble start starts not with systems or titles, but with people with small
strange beautiful moments that catch you off guard and with a single moment at a window showing me
not just the beginning of her story but of mine oh oh yeah how confusing those old women who
still believed in god i didn't like that because it's like old women do believe like they are like
you know somehow like more religious or like they're allowed to be though like if she said it like it was stupid
Well, you know, you can take it like you want, I don't know, she sounds like a barrier like, you know, she was someone that's going into a different religion, trying to help refugees and stuff, you know, I'm sure she's has some good, pretty good heart, no matter what her religion, but.
the
Pinocchio, I don't have strings. Look it up. It's like two minutes long. It's Pinocchio singing
Oh, that's the greatest
That's not me my boys used to play all the time
No, I don't have strength. Yeah, bro
Cuz that's bullshit. You know what that represents? That means that heifers don't own us
I don't have strength you heifer of bitches because the heifers try to keep us on drinks
That song is monumental. It's two minutes and 19 seconds long
I don't have strength. I just cut this visual of you in a bunch of fucking homies driving around
That's the stuff, Pinocchio.
Your KT, if you're listening, this is for you, bitch.
No, you're talking.
Come on, slowpoke.
All right, you're home.
Well, well, Pinocchio.
What's your rush I gotta be doing it home. Oh, this guy's park
I don't want to be an actor strong boy was terrible. He was yeah, he locked me in a bird cage
You poor boy, you must be a nervous wreck. That's it. You are a nervous wreck
Yeah, you're a nervous look at the wall. Oh, he's trying to get a brother
To box it
Just as I thought a slight touch of monetary complications with few colleagues the Maluna contraptions of applying trapezius
Say hippopotamus
I knew it compound transmission of the pandemonium with percussion and spasmodic frantic disintegration
Close your eyes. What do you see nothing open them now? What do you see?
Now that hot oh
My goodness
A palpitating syncopation to gilla-gilla with a wiki wacky stabbing of the
wiki wacky oh
This makes it
allergic yes and there is only one cure a vacation on Pleasure Island Pleasure
Island yes that happy land of carefree boys where every day is a holiday but I
can't go I play of course you can go I'm giving you my ticket he's talking
I insist, your health comes first.
Come, the coast departs at midnight.
I did indeed.
It's plazorile for me.
Where every day is a holiday,
and kids have nothing to do with playing.
Yo, who's the wolf? That's our landmaster computer.
Who's Jiminy Book Crippet?
Huh? Pinocchio!
Who's the wolf, bro?
When Pinocchio lies,
That wasn't a song by the way, but that was great
This is a no strings ace me and Brooklyn audit will play this every night and KT, you know KT
She's up comes up that Katie girl
And we were we were playing for her and yeah
Telling the heifers like you don't run a bitch
But I told you, huh?
He's surrounded by the hapers. They're going to put strings on him.
I was carrying a self-hearsal here.
We brought Jiminy Cricket's cast.
Don't go to World Go Blues. There's a Russian world down there.
Jiminy Cricket.
fucking get them in the closet
there are no stings on me
okay
I got one more on the scene, let me see, I want to see the cat and the fox one more time
the cat and the fox, because they're kind of funny, you know the cat doesn't talk very much but the fox
is a little talking, let me see
This is, uh, um, yeah, this one's good, I think.
It's great to be a celebrity, an actor's life for me
And act as life for me.
And the dummy fell for it.
Hooked lion and sinker.
And he still thinks when he's friends.
Domboly Pay.
Palantins.
That shows you how low honest John will stoop.
Oh, uh, Coachman?
What's your proposition?
Well...
How would you blokes like to make some real money?
Well, well...
No, no. Nothing like that. You see?
Selecting stupid little boys. Stupid little boys.
You know, the disobedient ones won't play your game from school.
Oh.
And you see...
Yes!
pleasure island pleasure island pleasure island at the law suppose they no no
there is no risk they never come back as boys
Yes, chief.
I'll pay you well.
I got plenty of gold.
Watch out for Coach Men, I guess.
That's like the Jeffrey Epstein of his day.
But that wasn't in the 60s or 50s.
I mean, isn't that crazy?
But I like that blue fairy, though.
She kept him honest, you know.
Well, he did get a very big nose, but you can hear
Stig speaking with this in no one accident.
Oh, yeah.
That was ghost
Yeah, the stupid little boys
Yeah, I could watch that all night all those old Disney movies. Yeah, I could watch that forever
Yeah, I mean, it's like I mean, I'd love
Even if you watch like Little Mermaid, it's like there's so many good of lessons like you know now a days
Areal Ariel had a good contract lawyer
She would have gotten out of that that contract with Ursula because that would go to a fork was called a spindle a rule or something
Jimmy
or dildo collection, not really important students, but that's the adult version of that.
Prince Eric, right? Now that's a man, huh? How's that for portraying a man?
that he can be with that
Eric is he was I think he's one of the cuter princes but he was like the perfect man Prince Eric I mean that he can be with that
Danny he was so dumb he like he didn't remember that Terry like Vanessa who's like you know just Ursula in disguise and so
doesn't matter talk about the jawline in the hair they don't give a fuck he could be dumb as a fucking tree
but he's fucking you know he looks like my noodle
it looks like my noodle back in the 80s
Gaston was cute too, but then nobody wants to marry Gaston
You know they want to marry Beast because you know Beast was here
Well Beast well, that's the point of Beast to show you that it doesn't matter if you're ugly as fuck
If you're funny and genuine you can still win love
Curse and that might be the reason for all the all everything that's wrong, you know, you never know
We just curse Jesus
the flower the rose and she kept and then she hid like you know find somebody to fall in love with
him for him you mean a witch like a real witch like betta like a witch witch met betta and that's
well if you're like watch the cartoon Beauty and the Beast that's like the real story Beauty and the
Beast and yes a witch yeah but betta is a real witch be that she is a witch and betta I think
a wizard of Oz that is betta that witch that's betta Margaret Hamilton like she's like a young
but you know what no that's better I said so I so I told you I got a bunch of these pictures of beta
so I and I showed I shared that one where she's in the grin oh she's
what come now did you put over her ass in the air she was
mildly on Christmas day and I don't even know I didn't know his name but she was saying no but
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Okay, I mean honestly, I would love nothing for you to be friends with her again
Cuz I know how much you like her or love her for whatever reason
Never happened the donkey will not get the carrot. I had exactly so
Let it go by the time I like
By the time the Persian spell wore off the carrot was already tied on on a fishing pole and she was riding me on the back
Don't don't bitch. I like a Roy's don't be a psyche psyche. I get it. I get it
I can imagine six months of that psyche. I love you. I love you. You fell in love with the dumb bitch
Psychi and now she's like thank you. Don't ever call me again. And now you're like, ah heartbroken. I got the fuck
I get it man
but don't get her back bro, don't you know how women work?
I'm gonna tell you how to get her back, ignore the dumb bitch.
If you stop talking about her for two weeks, she's gonna come back sucking your cock.
But the fact that you talk about her every day, which is already more.
Ignore the dumb bitch, the psychology one-on-one with women.
And then she'll come back to you.
you just have to be strong for like two to three weeks
she'll come running back to you trust me
because she's trying to turn me into like um
what you do now
oh I saw what are you now I saw something
you're someone else now
no they turned you into someone who the fuck
Where are your you come fool your bro, please somebody there is something